https://aquaterra.in/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentBlogCalendarUpcoming DeparturesHimalayan Adventure Challenge (HAC 2020)Kuari Pass TrekMarkha Valley Winter TrekKilimanjaro Remote Northern Route with African SafariKayak Clinic – GangaTreksFixed DeparturesComfort SeriesSignature TripsJordan AdventureAuden’s Col TrekKang Yatse II ClimbParang La TrekDayara Bugyal TrekBy RegionUttarakhandAuden’s Col TrekTons Homestay TrekHar Ki DunKuari Pass TrekPangarchulla ClimbDodital Lake TrekDayara Bugyal TrekGarhwal Trek-n-RaftBali Pass TrekTraill’s Pass TrekBaraadsar Lake TrekRuinsara Lake TrekBandarpunch ClimbPanpatia Col TrekDodital Hanumanchatti TrekKirti Gangotri Glacier TrekKuari Pass North Face TrekLadakhMarkha Valley Winter TrekChadar – The Frozen Zanskar River TrekMarkha Valley TrekSham Valley Winter TrekSham Valley TrekKang Yatse II ClimbInternational TripsGeorgia AdventureAconcagua ClimbKilimanjaro Remote Northern Route with African SafariDagala TrekGokyo Lakes TrekEverest Base Camp (EBC) and Gokyo Lakes TrekElbrus ClimbJordan AdventurePeru AdventureFutaleufu Multi AdventureMorocco Deserts and RiversZambezi Rafting & Luangwa SafariSafety, Equipment & Trip ArrangementsRiver RaftingFixed DeparturesSignature TripsZanskar River Rafting ExpeditionBrahmaputra River Rafting ExpeditionSubansiri River Rafting ExpeditionKali Sarda Rafting ExpeditionUpper Alaknanda River Rafting ExpeditionGarhwal Trek-n-RaftBy RegionUttarakhandTons Thriller Rafting ExpeditionTotal Tons Rafting ExpeditionLower Tons Rafting ExpeditionKali Sarda Rafting ExpeditionLadakhZanskar River Rafting ExpeditionArunachal / AssamBrahmaputra River Rafting ExpeditionSubansiri River Rafting ExpeditionLife on a RiverSafety, Equipment & FAQ’sOur PropertiesAtali GangaOur CampsCamp AquaterraCamp BagiCamp JungaCamp SitlakhetCamp TamiaCamp TirthanCamp YercaudHimalayan Adventure ChallengeCoursesIndia Mountaineering CourseSwiftwater / Flood Rescue Technician CourseBasic Mountain Skills CourseKayak Clinic – GangaSki Clinic GulmargAboutWhy UsBest Adventure Travel Companies on EarthChosen Outfitter & EndorsementsGreat Ascents & DescentsAquaterra Charity TrustMeet Our TeamThe Stalwart ProgramSchool GroupsAnglingExpeditionsMountain Rivers & StreamsPredator AnglingContactMain MenuInstagram page opens in new windowFacebook page opens in new windowTripAdvisor page opens in new windowYouTube page opens in new windowWebsite page opens in new windowBlogCalendarUpcoming DeparturesHimalayan Adventure Challenge (HAC 2020)Kuari Pass TrekMarkha Valley Winter TrekKilimanjaro Remote Northern Route with African SafariKayak Clinic – GangaTreksFixed DeparturesComfort SeriesSignature TripsJordan AdventureAuden’s Col TrekKang Yatse II ClimbParang La TrekDayara Bugyal TrekBy RegionUttarakhandAuden’s Col TrekTons Homestay TrekHar Ki DunKuari Pass TrekPangarchulla ClimbDodital Lake TrekDayara Bugyal TrekGarhwal Trek-n-RaftBali Pass TrekTraill’s Pass TrekBaraadsar Lake TrekRuinsara Lake TrekBandarpunch ClimbPanpatia Col TrekDodital Hanumanchatti TrekKirti Gangotri Glacier TrekKuari Pass North Face TrekLadakhMarkha Valley Winter TrekChadar – The Frozen Zanskar River TrekMarkha Valley TrekSham Valley Winter TrekSham Valley TrekKang Yatse II ClimbInternational TripsGeorgia AdventureAconcagua ClimbKilimanjaro Remote Northern Route with African SafariDagala TrekGokyo Lakes TrekEverest Base Camp (EBC) and Gokyo Lakes TrekElbrus ClimbJordan AdventurePeru AdventureFutaleufu Multi AdventureMorocco Deserts and RiversZambezi Rafting & Luangwa SafariSafety, Equipment & Trip ArrangementsRiver RaftingFixed DeparturesSignature TripsZanskar River Rafting ExpeditionBrahmaputra River Rafting ExpeditionSubansiri River Rafting ExpeditionKali Sarda Rafting ExpeditionUpper Alaknanda River Rafting ExpeditionGarhwal Trek-n-RaftBy RegionUttarakhandTons Thriller Rafting ExpeditionTotal Tons Rafting ExpeditionLower Tons Rafting ExpeditionKali Sarda Rafting ExpeditionLadakhZanskar River Rafting ExpeditionArunachal / AssamBrahmaputra River Rafting ExpeditionSubansiri River Rafting ExpeditionLife on a RiverSafety, Equipment & FAQ’sOur PropertiesAtali GangaOur CampsCamp AquaterraCamp BagiCamp JungaCamp SitlakhetCamp TamiaCamp TirthanCamp YercaudHimalayan Adventure ChallengeCoursesIndia Mountaineering CourseSwiftwater / Flood Rescue Technician CourseBasic Mountain Skills CourseKayak Clinic – GangaSki Clinic GulmargAboutWhy UsBest Adventure Travel Companies on EarthChosen Outfitter & EndorsementsGreat Ascents & DescentsAquaterra Charity TrustMeet Our TeamThe Stalwart ProgramSchool GroupsAnglingExpeditionsMountain Rivers & StreamsPredator AnglingContact Privacy PolicyYou are here:HomePrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how Aquaterra Adventures (I) Pvt. Ltd. uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.Aquaterra Adventures is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.Aquaterra Adventures may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1 June, 2009.What we collect?We may collect the following information:name and email addressdemographic information such as postcodepreferences and interests other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offersWhat we don’t Collect?Banking Information – Any Credit Card information you provide is processed by our payment gateway providers. We do not collect any sensitive information. You may provide this on our trusted payment gateway providers website: Instamojo or Razorpay while making a payment to reserve your spot on an expedition. Please check the terms and conditions of the Payment Gateway website to know more about their policies about your data.What we do with the information we gather?We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keeping.We may use the information to improve our products and services.We may periodically send promotional email about new or upcoming adventure holidays, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone (SMS or Whatsapp) or e-mail.We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.SecurityWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.You may contact us on info@aquaterra.in should you have any questions about this privacy policyLatest from the BlogUnlock 3 – Uttarakhand State Guidelines for TravellersAugust 5, 2020Covid-19 Mitigation and Operating PlanJune 9, 2020Covid-19: Safe PracticesJune 9, 2020Aquaterra makes it to the 2020 Outlook Responsible Tourism Awards LonglistJune 9, 2020Adventure Trails – Brahmaputra : Live MintJune 9, 2020Winter Wanderings – Chadar Trek : Business StandardJune 9, 2020Send us an EnquiryName * E-mail * Country City MessageSubmit
One of India's Premier Adventure Travel Company since 1995Terms & Conditions | Privacy Policy | Payments| Booking Form Go to Top
